{
    "subject": "resource/Ibrahim_al-Jaafari",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Mosul",
    "human_readable": "Ibrahim al-Jaafari attended the University of Mosul.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.987664520740509,
            "question": "Did Ibrahim al-Jaafari attend a university called Mosul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9870476722717285,
            "question": "Was Ibrahim al-Jaafari's education at the University of Mosul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9748947024345398,
            "question": "Name the university attended by Ibrahim al-Jaafari."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9572474360466003,
            "question": "Which university was attended by Ibrahim al-Jaafari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9368186593055725,
            "question": "Where did Ibrahim al-Jaafari attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8588312864303589,
            "question": "Ibrahim al-Jaafari's educational background includes attending which university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8183166980743408,
            "question": "What university did Ibrahim al-Jaafari go to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.731168806552887,
            "question": "Is Ibrahim al-Jaafari a student?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6886829733848572,
            "question": "What is the name of the institution Ibrahim al-Jaafari studied at?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6568337678909302,
            "question": "What is the name of the institution that Ibrahim al-Jaafari studied at?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ibrahim al-Jaafari attended the University of Mosul.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3589_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the institution Ibrahim al-Jaafari studied at?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3589_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ibrahim al-Jaafari a student?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3589_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university did Ibrahim al-Jaafari go to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3589_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3589_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Ibrahim Jaafari's attendance at the University of Mosul, where he earned his medical degree."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Ibrahim al-Jaafari was educated at Mosul university as a medical doctor, which supports the triple stating that he attended the University of Mosul."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}